International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Stulberg, Louis, General Secretary-Treasurer. Correspondence, 1956-1966, 1959-1966 (bulk). 5780/003.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- I. Subject files.
  - Local 177, N.Y.C.: 1956., Ladies' Garment Alteration Workers' Union. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Local 190, Philadelphia: 1955-58., Knitgoods Workers Union. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Local Union Managers' Meetings (New York locals): 1955-56., Includes notices and minutes of meetings (April 6 and Nov. 16, 1955). (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - March of Dimes Campaign: 1959-61., Includes correspondence with National Foundation, March of Dimes, collections, posters and publications. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - March of Dimes: 1956-58. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - March on Washington (for Jobs and Freedom): 1963., Correspondence with officers re organizing March, financial matters, pamphlets and publications issued by March. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Medstore Plan, Inc. and Drug Plan: Feb. 1961-62., Correspondents include Bernard Englander (president pro-tem), Med, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Medstore Plan, Inc.: Jan. 1961., Letters from pharmacists requesting Union not to open retail union discount pharmacies (Medstore). (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Medstore Plan: 1960., Includes minutes of meetings and agreements. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence., A-D. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, E-I. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, J-N. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, O-S (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, T-Z (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Niagara Falls Project: 1950-56., Includes Union statement submitted by James Lipsig to the Power Authority of State of N.Y., opposing proposed contracts for the sale of the St. Lawrence power, Nov. 1956; also correspondence bet. Herbert Lehman (governor) and J. Lipsig re project. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Resignations: 1962., N.Y. Cloak and Dress Joint Boards, Locals 10, 20, and 22. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Resignations: 1962., N.Y. Locals 25, 30, 32, 35, 38, 40, 48, 60-60A, 62, 64, and 66. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Resignations: 1962., N.Y. Locals 82, 89, 91, 98, 99, 102, 105, 117, 132, 142, and 155. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Resignations: 1962., Northeast Dept. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Resignations: 1962., Cloak-out-of-Town Dept., Eastern Region. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Resignations: 1962., Central States, Southwest and Mid-West Regions. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Resignations: 1962., Southeast and Ohio-Kentucky Regions, and Pacific Coast. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Resignations: 1962, Upper South, Canada, Philadelphia, Boston, Puerto Rico, President and General Secretary-Treasurer. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Resignations: 1956, Composite list of all locals of the ILGWU. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, N.Y.C.: 1961-62, Includes Harry Krugman's report, cases, reports for the Retirement Fund and the Health, Welfare and Severance Fund and Board of Trustees minutes. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Fund, Coat and Suit Industry, N.Y.C.: 1958-60. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Fund, Coat and Suit Industry, N.Y.C.: May 1957-Aug, 1958. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Staff Retirement Fund: 1955-56., Includes financial statements and minutes. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Training Institute, ILGWU: 1956-60, Includes Gus Tyler reports. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Union Health Center, NYC: 1956-61., Includes correspondence with Center's director. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Union Health Center, NYC: 1961-62., Accident claims (sample copies). (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Union Health Center, NYC: 1955-58., Complaints. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Union Health Center, NYC: 1960-63., Financial reports. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Union Health Center, NYC: 1956-59., Financial reports. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Union Health Center, NYC: 1958-61., Labor contracts. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Union Health Center, NYC: 1955-56., Minutes. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - United Housing Foundation: 1966. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - United Housing Foundation: 1954-65. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Unity House: 1958., Includes accident reports and rules and regulations for dining room personnel. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Unity House: Sept. 1961., Employers weekend. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Unity House: 1956, Employers weekend. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Unity House: 1954-61., Mendes vs. ILGWU and Pike County Hotel. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Unity House: 1954-61., Mendes vs. ILGWU. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board: 1955-64. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- II. Personal correspondence.
  - Louis Stulberg, Personal: 1962. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - L.S., Personal: 1961. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - L.S., Personal: 1960. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - L.S., Personal: 1959. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - L.S., Personal: 1959., Re Morris Isman estate. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - L.S., Personal: 1958. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - L.S., Personal: 1957. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - L.S., Personal: 1956. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - L.S., Personal: 1955. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - L.S., Personal:, Newspaper clipping files. (Box 28, Folder 10)